Design Head

NITIN CHAVAN

Row house no.1, Yash garden, Indirayni Nagar, Bhosari, Pune - 411039 9890 67 0003 | nitin@weblabssolutions.com www.weblabssolutions.com

Summary

Award-winning graphic designer and art director experienced with web and multimedia, corporate identity, print collateral, packaging, advertising. Comfortable with information architecture, project management and business development.

Recent Work (My Designs)

Websites

www.arrowhead-connect.com

www.bizhelpcorp.com

www.irianamusic.com

www.sanskarpratishthan.com

www.sunminds.net

www.balajisecurity.in

www.kohinoorgrouppune.com/newsite

www.aarindiamo.com

www.weblabssolutions.com/clients/aamba

www.weblabssolutions.com/clients/knowledge-forum/website.html

www.imagene.co.in

www.icaptive.in

www.spaceageassociates.biz

www.qbixacademia.com

www.prowessengg.com

www.ishanindustries.net

www.saswad.com

Logo & Graphics Design

http://weblabssolutions.com/logo http://weblabssolutions.com/logo/stationary.html

Professional Experience

1st Sep. 2007 to present -Design Head, Art Director Weblabs Solutions,
Pune

+ Production of print, identity, packaging, multimedia, web design and web applications

Design Head

- + Interacting and follow up with Clients
- + Trained, supervised and provided art direction for junior designers
- + Managed multiple, concurrent projects in different stages
- + Designed information architecture and user interface for on-screen applications
- + Demonstrated ability to learn and use new technology.

16th Jan. 2006 to 1st Sep. 2007, - **Team Lead Crest Pre-media Solutions**, Viman Nagar, Pune

- + Performed lead role in the design and production of print, identity, packaging, multimedia, web design and web applications
- + Managed press checks, art directed photos, supervised team design efforts
- + Trained, supervised and provided art direction for junior designers
- + Managed multiple, concurrent projects in different stages
- + Designed information architecture and user interface for on-screen applications
- + Demonstrated ability to learn and use new technology.

18th Jun. 2001 to 14th Jan. 2006, - Graphic Designer TeamNet Pvt. Ltd, Kothrud, Pune

- + Production of print media, identity, multimedia, web design.
- + Managed multiple, concurrent projects in different stages
- + Designed information architecture and user interface for on-screen applications
- + Demonstrated ability to learn and use new technology.

1st Nov. 2000 to 17th Jun. 2001, **-Faculty Infoway Technology**, Kothrud, Pune

- + Trained and supervised for students
- + Production of print media, identity, multimedia, web design.

Education

Advance diploma in software engineering from Aptech, Pune. Masters in Web Designing from Insite, Pune.

B.Com from Garware College of commerce in Yr.2002-03 from Pune University. H. S. C. from Garware College of commerce in Yr. 2000 from Maharashtra Board. S. S. C. from Kendriya Vidyalaya (Belgaum) in Yr. 1997 from C.B.S.E. Board.

Design Head

Skill Set

Excellent skills in Photoshop, Illustrator, Flash and Dreamweaver. Experienced with HTML5, CSS3, Java Script and Action Script 2. Strong troubleshooting skills, familiar with cross-browser and cross-platform issues, comfortable with Mac or Windows.

Personal Information

Date of Birth: 31th May 1979

Corresponding Address: Row house no.1, Yash garden, Indirayni Nagar, Bhosari, Pune

- 411039

Marital Status: Married Sex: Male

Linguistic Proficiency: English, Marathi, Hindi.

Hobbies: Music, Cricket, Mountain trekking, Computer Games.

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that all the information furnished is true to the best of my knowledge.

Date: 06 Mar. 2013

Place: Pune (Nitin

Chavan)